<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Karan&#39;s blog</title>
        <link>https://karans.sh/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Karan&#39;s blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 22:24:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://karans.sh/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>RIP Alex</title>
        <link>https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 22:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You were the sweetest cat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex wasn’t just another community cat in E-Block. He was the presence at night to look out for. If any resident ever walked by the back side of the block, they probably saw him on top of a red Maruti Swift, which was the &amp;ldquo;spot&amp;rdquo;. Always. Typical cat fashion, overlooking his kingdom from the top. Unlike Chess, who always kept a little distance, Alex wanted you to know he was there. He wasn’t shy, he’d look right at you, purr, and make sure you noticed him. But only if you locked eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, one of the fondest parts of my day for the past couple of years was heading down at 11pm to feed Alex and Chess. Chess would hang back, cautious, hiding somewhere nearby. Alex, though, was never like that. He’d sit up on the car, waiting, calm but alert. As soon as I showed up, he’d acknowledge me in his own way — a sound, a purr, that little body language that said, “I know you’re here.” Those nights became a routine I really looked forward to. Unfortunately, that has come to an end now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of residents cared for him, and he gave back by being a great companion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s why it hurts so much to write this. A few days ago, Alex was in a car accident. It wasn’t anyone’s fault. Sometimes these things happen with animals. But even knowing that doesn’t make it easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now when I walk past that red Swift, it feels wrong not to see him there. I still expect him to be stretched out, watching everything like he always did. I’ve got so many photos and videos of him, and while I’m grateful for them, looking at them right now just brings back the ache of losing him. Taken away from us, far too soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex was more than a cat in the block. He was part of my life over the last few years. He mattered. And he’s going to be missed more than words can really say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rest in peace, Alex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;video-wrapper&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; 
            src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/F3Bnk3ixUww&#34; 
            allowfullscreen 
            title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;
    &gt;
    &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alex and Chess having dinner&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/alex-chess-dinner.png&#34;
	width=&#34;626&#34;
	height=&#34;1355&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/alex-chess-dinner_hua5fed4f30896c534af98f4bd865b3c07_1458313_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/alex-chess-dinner_hua5fed4f30896c534af98f4bd865b3c07_1458313_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;dinnertime for alex and chess&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;110px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alex, Chess and Lily having dinner together, featuring the swift&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/trinity.png&#34;
	width=&#34;626&#34;
	height=&#34;1355&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/trinity_hud57d50e0f1a31a7e1f69ffb430dd0fdc_1319479_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/trinity_hud57d50e0f1a31a7e1f69ffb430dd0fdc_1319479_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;holy trinity of dinner&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;110px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/yawn.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1016&#34;
	height=&#34;1355&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/yawn_hua8558958b48cfed04a1ef73fa7022395_2484448_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/yawn_hua8558958b48cfed04a1ef73fa7022395_2484448_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/stretch.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1016&#34;
	height=&#34;1355&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/stretch_hu5106d17bb13e23537f56b612ed077b9d_1145212_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/stretch_hu5106d17bb13e23537f56b612ed077b9d_1145212_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;stretch&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/pets.png&#34;
	width=&#34;762&#34;
	height=&#34;1355&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/pets_hud517aea81525a6872dd34b33b1c94aad_1315310_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/pets_hud517aea81525a6872dd34b33b1c94aad_1315310_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;pets&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;56&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;134px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/loaf.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1016&#34;
	height=&#34;1355&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/loaf_hu19681c7d758a1c0e6419cfe98361b157_1362222_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://karans.sh/p/rip-alex/loaf_hu19681c7d758a1c0e6419cfe98361b157_1362222_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;loaf&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;rest well buddy, you will be missed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>RAR file format and Linux - a silly rant</title>
        <link>https://karans.sh/p/rar-file-format-and-linux-a-silly-rant/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 19:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://karans.sh/p/rar-file-format-and-linux-a-silly-rant/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I want to preface this by saying that I dont care about the whole &amp;ldquo;year of the linux desktop&amp;rdquo; stuff that this will eventually get into but the reality is, I daily drive linux on my personal device, so some minor stuff pisses me off. If I was to achieve this on windows, it wouldnt exactly be a cake walk either for the average user. Still, they&amp;rsquo;d have to download a program such as winrar or 7zip and then just be done with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What bothers me is I - or in this case - the average power user, if facing this scenario, would have to get into the terminal and apt install stuff. Yhat is just annoying, and not good ux. especially; not if you want to appeal to mass market users eventually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-actual-problem---multi-part-archives-in-rar-format&#34;&gt;The actual problem - multi part archives in rar format
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, with the default file explorer, you cant extract multi part archives, there is a file roller app, but it doesnt have the unrar package.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, you must install it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-shell&#34; data-lang=&#34;shell&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;sudo apt install unrar
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;and now, you can unpack them with file roller! cool, but how the hell will &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; users figure this out. They will end up installing bogus programs when they dont need to.
I guess, a lot of linux stuff is designed by developers for developers, which causes these things. The error message is not helpful at all: &amp;ldquo;too small block encountered 0 bytes&amp;rdquo; - what does this mean for the average user? I would just assume the rar file is corrupt!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There should be a way to do this without the user needing to meddle into the terminal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ideally, it should just say: &amp;ldquo;hey! you need to install this, click here&amp;rdquo;, do it&amp;rsquo;s thing and then let user get to whatever they are doing&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe one day, it will be so simple. One day&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Weight Loss tips for the vegetarian urban techie Indian crowd</title>
        <link>https://karans.sh/p/weight-loss-tips-for-the-vegetarian-urban-techie-indian-crowd/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://karans.sh/p/weight-loss-tips-for-the-vegetarian-urban-techie-indian-crowd/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost around 24 KG weight this year, going from 104 -&amp;gt; 80 KG, all while maintaining an occasional saatvik diet. Having said that, the title does sound clickbait-y but I have definitely not had onion, garlic etc for many, many days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, most of these tips can be used by vegetarians too! Most of what I am going to point out in this article has been written a 100 times by others, but my experience is around an urban setting, Bengaluru specifically. Anyway, without going on and on about the justification, here&amp;rsquo;s what worked for me, which may or may not work for you. :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-you-stay-matters-the-most&#34;&gt;Where you stay matters the most
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban india is in shambles. Roads are non-existent and broken, and going out will literally kill you. Infrastructure is a real problem, and cribbing about it will not help. What helps is, you have to stay in your bubble. Gated societies are your friend here. When you filter out where you live, have these as non-negotiables:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A gym which is decently equipped and has hygienic toilets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You dont need a fancy gym or expensive equipment, but look for basic set of weights, machines, and make sure the toilet is clean! At most good societies this will not be a problem but make it a point to check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A walking path&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there might not be a dedicated walking path in most older societies, private walkways across blocks are regularly used by residents for their morning and evening walk. This should be present in most societies with more than 3 blocks. Filter for those.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A swimming pool&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is very contrarian but IF YOU CAN SWIM, then having a good pool is a big big help in getting a good workout in, especially in summer time when the heat is a problem. I personally prefer evening swims, around 6-8 PM, but you can filter out times based on what works for you. So if you can&amp;rsquo;t swim - my suggestion is, whenever it is summer time, sign up to learn. Apart from learning a new skill, you gain a cardio workout that you can do anytime you prefer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;food&#34;&gt;Food
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weight loss is done on a two prong scale, most people will try to do 50% of their effort in exercise and the rest on food. However, 80% of the battle is in maintaining your diet in the correct way and not deviating from it. I have had my challenges, but here&amp;rsquo;s what has worked and what hasn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whey is your friend: Make a note of this, and regardless of your exercise levels, start having whey + water. It is 100% saatvik and you can definitely have it. However, which brand is a big question that comes up here. My favourite clean ones are maxn, muscle nectar and the whole truth(Look online for coupon codes, for all three). Now there are variations after variations, and there are non-flavoured ones as well. I am a chocolate person, so whatever chocolate flavoured whey I like, I consume.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have curd or chaash and have it everyday. Curd is an excellent probiotic and gut friendly too. Has decent amount of protein.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paneer/Tofu/Soya: These three foods are also a must to include. Do not give me shit about soya and the other controversies, stfu and eat it. Thanks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water, 3-4L of it a day. Do not buy those big ass 2L bottles. Those are plastic and not good anyway. You dont need anything fancy. get a good 1L copper bottle, make sure you do the mental math to finish it thrice or four times. Just carry it around.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have cravings for fried food, make them in an air frier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A fruit a day is compulsory, try apples or pomegranates, but any fiber rich fruit is great.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get used to eating 1 roti instead of two or three. Eat lots of veggies and dal, but not too much. Add a protein source in your lunch and dinner. Once, it could be curd, another time, it could be paneer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get your macros right. Get your BMR, and plan meals to keep it just below that rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lots of cucumbers in salads are excellent choices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;walk-a-lot&#34;&gt;Walk, a lot!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel like among all the discourse around food and activity levels, people forget that we can walk too. Try to do 10-11K steps a day. The more the better! I do 15K a day on average. Yes, it is quite a lot initially, so ramp it up slowly. Once you start doing it you will enjoy it a lot, and since you are in a society, stick to a regular time. You&amp;rsquo;ll even make friends if you are not too scared to talk to actual real humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally prefer to walk at nights, since it is much more quieter. But you can do whatever works for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;exercise&#34;&gt;Exercise!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bit of strength training goes a long way, regardless of your gender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I am not an expert and will not go into depths on push/pull etc. &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;fmhy.net&#34; &gt;fmhy.net&lt;/a&gt; has an entire section dedicated to fitness, go check it out and create a plan for yourself. Or you could be like me and hire someone to help with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s what I do. You dont really have to follow what I do, but I hope this helps if you are someone totally new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;warmup&#34;&gt;Warmup
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fire Hydrant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glute Bridges&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cat-Cow&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lying Leg Rotations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T - Spine Kneeling Flexion/Extension&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tempo Counter Balance Squat 5:10:1:1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arm Circles (forwards and backwards)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lat Tricep Stretch&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;T - Spine Rotations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wall Slides&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-1--cardio--circuit-training&#34;&gt;Day 1 ( Cardio &amp;amp; Circuit training)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Farmer walk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burpees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jumping Jacks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dumbell Thruster&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treadmill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cycling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-2--full-body&#34;&gt;Day 2 ( Full Body)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;chest press machine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shoulder press&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;leg extension&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pushdown triceps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seated rowing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;dumbell biceps curl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treadmill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-3--cardio--circuit-training&#34;&gt;Day 3 ( Cardio &amp;amp; Circuit training)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Farmer walk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burpees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jumping Jacks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dumbell Thruster&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treadmill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cycling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-4-chestshouldertriceps&#34;&gt;Day 4 (Chest,Shoulder,Triceps)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;chest press machine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dumbell incline chest press&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over head triceps extension&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skull crusher&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lateral raise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Front raise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chest fly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treadmill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-5-leg&#34;&gt;Day 5 (Leg)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barbell Squat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goblet Squat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leg extension&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;leg curl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calf raise&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flutter kicks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treadmill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-6--back-biceps&#34;&gt;Day 6 ( Back, Biceps)
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lat pulldown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dumbell biceps curl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;preacher curl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;single arm dumbell rowing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;hammer curl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cable pulldown lats&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treadmill&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>No JavaScript? No Problem.</title>
        <link>https://karans.sh/p/no-javascript-no-problem./</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:17:38 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://karans.sh/p/no-javascript-no-problem./</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In all honesty, I was repulsed by the idea of having a website for myself, where I showcase all the things I do. I don&amp;rsquo;t really think I needed a website just to show people the &amp;ldquo;things&amp;rdquo; that I create. After all, the things I generally create don&amp;rsquo;t have fancy UI&amp;rsquo;s that one can browse online and marvel at. I generally write backend systems, and deploying those things takes a lot of time, and I &lt;em&gt;doubt&lt;/em&gt; someone interested would actually take the trouble.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;do-i-even-need-a-website&#34;&gt;Do I even need a website?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s just easier to give people a link to a github account, and hand off the problem to someone else. You go to &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; site, and &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; figure out if you like the work that I do. If you need clarifications, you can create an issue, or ping me somewhere, or e-mail me. Should be easy enough, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s still nice to have a presence on the web, even if it is ephemeral, and the website may die down and burn to the ground one day. So, I have this nice fancy domain, that matches my username everywhere, which makes it easier to find me. I think it could come handy some day if I actually do some amazing stuff that I&amp;rsquo;d want to talk about. The kinda content that goes crazy on hacker news and the likes of reddit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-would-a-website-made-by-me-entirely-look-like&#34;&gt;What would a website made by me entirely look like?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look, it&amp;rsquo;s no secret, my knowledge of javascript is&amp;hellip; lacklustre. Which seems like madness, every developer should have a rough idea of what it is, right? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to go about life and earn money without ever writing a single line of javascript code that ran on production. Yes, I&amp;rsquo;ve done a few changes here and there for testing stuff locally, but nothing that I would count as impactful. I dont know vuejs,reactjs or any of the other million or so frameworks that are &lt;em&gt;hot&lt;/em&gt;. I simply don&amp;rsquo;t have to care about them for now. So, this website has ZERO javascript. Yep, nothing. Not even analytics. I know most of people who would ever read this would be bots anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-would-i-add-here&#34;&gt;What would I add here?
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I currently use Obsidian nearly exclusively for writing. I think I will get around to adding more content soon(maybe) and fix the site&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
